<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tea Time</string>
    <string name="welcome_text">Find teas by:</string>
    <string name="region_button">region</string>
    <string name="type_button">type</string>
    <string name="japan_button">japan</string>
    <string name="china_button">china</string>
    <string name="africa_button">africa/india</string>
    <string name="india_button">india</string>
    <string name="other_region_button">other</string>
    <string name="tea_black">black teas</string>
    <string name="tea_white_oolong">white teas/oolong teas</string>
    <string name="tea_green">green teas</string>
    <string name="tea_other">other teas</string>
    <string name="back_button">back</string>
    <string name="tea_desc">Fake stuff about a tea, \nThis is pretty interesting
                right? \nNo not really, just filling up space. \nHow much space does
                this take up?</string>
    <string name="gpg_desc">Chinese green tea from the Zhejiang province in eastern China.
        Its English name comes from the fact that the tightly rolled pellets resemble gunpowder.
        The rolling of the leaves helps prevent physical damage and breaking, as well as
        maintaining much of the flavour that would otherwise be lost.\n\nWhen purchasing
        gunpowder green tea, a shinier leaf is often representative of a fresher tea. Smaller
        pellet size is also a sign of higher-quality tea.</string>
    <string name="dw_desc">Also known as Lung Ching or Longjing. Chinese green tea from the
        Zhejiang province in eastern China. Leaves are pan-roasted shortly after picking to
        produce a smooth, floral flavour with a slightly toast aftertaste. In the most strictly
        authentic definition, true dragonwell tea comes only from the one area in the Hangzhou region
        of the Zhejiang province. A majority of dragonwell tea comes from other regions of the province,
        with a smaller amount being prepared with the same technique using leaves grown in other
        areas. An experienced drinker may be able to spot the difference, although it is not
        immediately noticeable in many cases. \n\nWhen purchasing Longjing tea, be sure to look for
        a region or area of origin if it is claimed to be authentic.</string>
    <string name="assam_desc">A traditional black tea from the Assam region of India, known as the
        world\'s largest tea growing region. Assam teas are produced from a specific variety of the
        tea plant, known as Camelia sinensis var assamica (a plant native to this region). This
        variety is represented by a malty flavour and strong bright colour. Most tea blends labeled
        as \'breakfast\' will contain Assam tea, and Irish breakfast is generally made of CTC
        (finely shredded) Assam leaves. Compared to other Indian tea-growing regions, plantations
        here are located closer to sea level, with other regions generally being located in the
        highlands. The geography here, combined with the large amount of rainfall and high temperatures
        contribute to Assam\'s characteristic malty flavour.\n\n\ It is worth noting some fun facts
        about the Assam plant and region- Tea plantations in the region are in a separate time zone
        from the rest of Indian Standard Time. Known as Tea Garden Time, it is one hour ahead of the
        IST. The region is also one of two in the world with a native tea plant, the other being
        southern China. The Assam plant was first introduced to the west by a Scotsman, Robert Bruce
        in the 1820s.</string>
    <string name="bdp_desc">A fragrant tea from the Yunnan province in southern China. Hand-rolled
        tippy black tea leaves produce a malty flavour with some hints of chocolate. Dragon pearls
        are generally rolled with very high quality leaves and buds to produce a full bodied cup.
        These leaves are capable of producing multiple steeps while maintaining much of the original
        flavour.</string>
    <string name="ceylon_desc">Ceylon teas vary depending on the altitude at which plants are grown.
        Plants grown at the lowest elevation are bolder, mid elevation are less bold but with a more
        rich flavour. Teas grown at the highest elevation are generally smooth with floral notes.
        The high-grown teas are considered to be the finest the area produces, though any authentic
        Ceylon tea is seen as high quality. These teas will carry the \'lion logo\', a highly
        practice which is highly regulated by the Sri Lanka Tea Board. Any tea with this logo has
        been thoroughly inspected to guarantee quality.
        \n\nThe three distinct regions of tea production are the Upcountry (Udarata), Mid country
        (Medarata) and Low country (Pahatha rata). </string>
    <string name="eg_desc">Traditionally a Chinese black tea flavoured with
        bergamot oil to produce a citrusy taste similar to many expensive Chinese teas. The origin
        of the blend varies based on different sources, though it is commonly accepted that it is
        named after Charles Grey, a Prime Minister of England in the 1830s. One story claims that
        Lord Grey once saved a Mandarin man from drowning. The man was so grateful he presented the
        tea as a gift.\n\nEarl Grey is the drink of choice for Captain Picard of the Federation
        starship Enterprise.</string>
    <string name="eb_desc">Traditionally a blend of Assam, Ceylon and Kenyan teas. The combination
        produces a strong, rich full-bodied drink often mixed with milk and sugar.\n\n A fun fact on
        English breakfast- the blend and name is considered to have originated not in England, but in
        colonial America around 1843.</string>
    <string name="gen_desc">Often colloquially referred to as \'popcorn tea\'. A Japanese green tea
        combined with toasted rice. During the roasting process, pieces of rice can pop, and end up
        resembling popcorn. The rice lends smooth flavour with a nutty aftertaste. The blend was
        originally drunk by Japanese peasants, the toasted rice acting as a filler to allow expensive
        tea to last longer. While most green teas are steeped in cooler water for a shorter period
        of time, genmaicha is best prepared with hot water. </string>
    <string name="dar_desc">The Darjeeling region is one of two major tea producing areas in India
        (the other being Assam). Unlike the Assam region which has it\'s own native plant,
        the Darjeeling region uses the traditional Chinese variant of the tea plant. Darjeeling teas
        generally produce a floral, fruity cup. These are often referred to as the \'champagne of
        tea\'. There are several distinct types of Darjeeling teas, each with their own characteristics:
        \n\nFirst Flush: harvested mid-March following spring rains. Produces a very light cup with a
        mild aroma. Often fruity, peachy with a honey aftertaste.
        \n\nSecond Flush: harvested from the same plants in June, produces a darker, more full-bodied
        cup. Citrusy, crisp with an apricot aftertaste.
        \n\nAutumnal Flush: harvested at the end of the rainy season in autumn. Full bodied, fruity
        aftertaste.
        \n\nWhile most Darjeeling teas were traditionally black, it is becoming more common to see
        whites and oolongs produced as well.</string>
    <string name="gyo_desc">Traditionally shade-grown Japanese tea, one of the highest grades the
        country produces. Though categorised as a type of sencha, the plants that produce gyokuro
        are protected from the sun for two to three weeks prior to the harvest. Those that produce
        sencha are left uncovered. The shade serves to increase the caffeine content of the leaf,
        also creating a sweeter flavour and fresher aroma when compared to traditional sencha. Gyokuro
        is also steeped differently than most other green teas- at about 60 degrees celsius for 90
        seconds. A larger amount of leaves are generally used as well.
        \n\nAbout 40% of gyokuro produced in Japan comes from the city of Yame.</string>
    <string name="hoj_desc">Unlike other Japanese green teas, hojicha is a roasted version of sencha.
        Traditionally the roasting was done in porcelain pots over charcoal, but much modern hojicha
        is roasted in electric drums similar to the coffee roasting process. This roasting alters the
        colour from green to a reddish-brown and gives a toasty, caramel-like flavour. The firing
        also reduces the caffeine content of the tea, making it a popular after dinner drink.
    </string>
    <string name="ib_desc">Irish breakfast is most commonly made of finely shredded Assam teas.
        It produces a very strong cup of dark red to brown colour. Milk and sugar are typically
        added though it can be consumed plain. </string>
    <string name="keemun_desc">Famous black tea from the Anhui province Eastern China. Produces a
        smooth, semi-sweet cup with hints of smokiness. It was first produced around 1875 and very
        quickly became popular in the west, where it can still be found combined with Assam and
        other black teas in blends like English breakfast. It is grown in a mountainous area at
        lower temperatures with a high humidity, contributing to its characteristic taste.
    \n\nThe most common type of Keemun is the Mao Feng variety. Harvested earlier in the year, it
        produces a sweeter, lighter tea than other varieties.
    \n\nThe Hao Ya variety, harvested later, lends itself to a much stronger tea.</string>
    <string name="ctc_desc">Finely shredded version of classic Kenyan tea. Similar to Irish breakfast,
        produces a strong, dark cup typically consumed with milk and sugar. CTC Kenyan teas are
        often used in blends with tea from India or China.</string>
    <string name="kenyan_desc">Tea was first cultivated in Kenya around 1904 using plants from India.
        Teas grown here typically produce a rich, dark red cup. Farms in Kenya are set at a
        high altitude where the climate is much less arid than closer to sea level. A large majority
        of tea produced here ends up in black tea blends or processed in the crush, tear, curl method
        (similar to Assam in Irish breakfast). Kenya is the fourth-largest worldwide producer of tea,
        90% of which is grown on small farming operations as opposed to large plantations.</string>
    <string name="yun_desc">Sometimes referred to as Dianhong, a typically high-end black tea from
        southern China. Yunnan teas from other Chinese black teas, as they often contain many more
        \'golden tips\' and fine buds. Most Yunnan teas will produce a dark orange cup with sweet
        aroma and slightly malty taste. The area produces several varieties dating back to the early
        19th century:
    \n\nYunnan Pure Gold: considered to be the finest tea grown in the region. Typically contains only
        golden tips, and when brewed creates a bright red cup with a sweet taste.
    \n\nYunnan Gold: contains fewer buds than its Pure Gold cousin. Brews to a brassy red colour,
        slightly less sweet than Pure Gold.
    \n\nBroken Yunnan: low-end Yunnan tea, most often bitter on its own and added to blends. Brews a
        dark red-brown cup and contains few to no golden tips.</string>
    <string name="kuk_desc">Highly popular Japanese green tea. Produced largely from the stems and
        stalks of the tea plants used to create sencha, it has a naturally low caffeine content when
        compared to other green teas. Produces a very fresh vegetable taste, slightly nutty and
        creamy. Brews to a light green colour somewhere between sencha and gyokuro. Unlike most other
        teas, kukicha is commonly steeped three or four times while maintaining most of its flavour.</string>
    <string name="plc_desc">Pi Luo Chun is renowned for it\'s delicate and unique appearance. Curled
        leaves resemble snail meat (the name literally translates to "green snail spring") and produce
        a very strong aroma. The taste is somewhat fruity and floral. The smell can be off-putting at
        first, and it\'s original name "scary fragrance" reflects this. Legend says the Kangxi Emperor
        visited a village where the tea was produced and gave it the more appealing name by which it
        is now known. Today, true Pi Luo Chun is cultivated in the Jiangsu province in eastern
        China, though it can also be found in the Zhejian and Sichuan provinces. These teas are generally
        a lower quality and contain larger leaves and produce a nuttier flavour.</string>
    <string name="sencha_desc">Sencha is the most popular tea in Japan, usually representing about
        80% of the country\'s tea production.</string>

</resources>
