<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tea Time</string>
    <string name="welcome_text">Find teas by:</string>
    <string name="region_button">region</string>
    <string name="type_button">type</string>
    <string name="japan_button">japan</string>
    <string name="china_button">china</string>
    <string name="africa_button">africa</string>
    <string name="india_button">india</string>
    <string name="other_region_button">other</string>
    <string name="tea_black">black teas</string>
    <string name="tea_white">white teas</string>
    <string name="tea_green">green teas</string>
    <string name="tea_oolong">oolong teas</string>
    <string name="tea_other">other teas</string>
    <string name="back_button">back</string>
    <string name="tea_desc">Fake stuff about a fake tea, \nThis is pretty interesting
                right? \nNo not really, just filling up space. \nHow much space does
                this take up?</string>
    <string name="gpg_desc">Chinese green tea from the Zhejiang province in eastern China.
        Its English name comes from the fact that the tightly rolled pellets resemble gunpowder.
        The rolling of the leaves helps prevent physical damage and breaking, as well as
        maintaining much of the flavour that would otherwise be lost.\n\nWhen purchasing
        gunpowder green tea, a shinier leaf is often representative of a fresher tea. Smaller
        pellet size is also a sign of higher-quality tea.</string>
    <string name="dw_desc">Also known as Lung Ching or Longjing. Chinese green tea from the
        Zhejiang province in eastern China. Leaves are pan-roasted shortly after picking to
        produce a smooth, floral flavour with a slightly toast aftertaste. For the true tea
        drinker, Dragonwell tea is produced only in the Hangzhou region of the Zhejiang province,
        though most will accept tea produced anywhere in the province as Dragonwell. An experienced
        drinker may be able to spot the difference, although it is not immediately noticeable in
        many cases. \n\nWhen purchasing Longjing tea, be sure to look for a region or area of origin
        if it is claimed to be authentic.</string>

</resources>
